this is a story of intuitive coverage
James is a fitness enthusiast
and that's how he met crystal in a park
they get coffee which leads to more than
just coffee if you know what we mean
when they decided to tie the knot we got
down to it our smart system detected
James's change in relationship status
then we sent him a timely online ad so
that we could start furthering a
relationship with him
so now James starts thinking about their
health coverage
James is definitely interested in
learning more about insurance policies
for his new family he gets to choose
from the agents that are nearby based on
agent profiles James chooses Brian our
facebook Messenger BOTS introduces the
to Brian first connects then arranges to
meet for coffee
[Music]
back home James chairs agent Brian's new
insurance proposal with Krystal together
they accept the proposal with a touch of
a button
and speaking of pushing buttons nine
months later baby Jessica is born he
loves on to extend cover for his new
arrival as an existing customer his
additional cover request is instantly
approved agent brian is notified of the
new cover and a familiar face
congratulate James now the whole family
has peace of mind for the future
Manulife intuitive cover for a better
future